# Neymar John

## Senior Software Engineer

**E-mail:** seriousman1994217winter@gmail.com Skype: live:.cid.f001faea3ab92d58

GitHub: https://github.com/neymarjohn Phone: +1 315 636 4392

I am honored to be here to show you about my skills and experiences.

My destination is to become the top ranked Software developer.

My customer's order is just law for me.

**My Skills**: Blockchain, Web3, Solidity, Solana, NFT, Smart contract, JavaScript, React, Angular, Vue, Node, Express, SQL, NoSQL, PHP, Laravel, CodeIgniter, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3, AJAX, JavaScript, SQL, XML, API Integration. I will always do my best to satisfy your demands and I feel great when I see my customer's satisfaction. I do care about all customers who want to build the Software.

My ultimate goal is to provide the best solution with high teamwork and to achieve the unity and success of the group.

#### **Skills**

| Coding understanding                          | Excellent |
|---|-----------|
| Blockchain                                    | Excellent |
| React   | Master    |
| Angular                                       | Master    |
| Vue   | Master    |
| Frontend                                      |           |
| Node JS                                       | Master    |
| Backend                                       | Master    |
| Ruby on Rails                                 | Master    |
| PHP(Laravel, Cl, Symphony)                    | Excellent |
| Mobile APP(React Native, IOS, Android, Ionic) | Master    |
|   | Master    |
| Java(Struts, Spring, Spring boot)             | Master    |

#### **Work History**

#### 2014-05 - 2015-08

#### Senior Full-Stack Developer

Marco, Zagreb, Croatia

My position in this job was to develop the frontend and backend as a full-stack developer.

The basic task was to develop rental apps such as Airbnb.

When the initial requirements were discussed with the client and the issue of specifying the development language was raised, he specified Laravel under the guise of a large-scale project. So I checked everything with him from the initial design to the data base design and started development.

When the development was nearing completion, he proposed a mobile version, and this project was sustained for nearly two years.

It was a really great project.

He succeeded in this project and the contract with me was successfully concluded.

#### 2015-10 - 2018-10

#### Full-Stack developer

**NetAngels** 

Worked full time web/desktop/mobile app in this company with developer.

Contributed to the design and implementation of new features and improvements to existing features.

Collaborated with cross-functional teams to gather requirements and implement new features

#### 2019-03 - 2020-05

## Senior Frontend and Backend Developer

Rafik, London, United Kingdom

My position in this job was to develop only the front end.

As a management app related to building maintenance, at first, only the frontend part was developed with react native in the project.

Then, considering the results of the backend part of the project were not good and the communication was unreasonable, I also took care of the backend part of this project. Results The project has been successful and is now operational.

#### 2020-07 – 2022-10 Senior Full-Stack developer

Sirplay

My position in this job was to develop the front end with using web3 or eth.

In this here I developed smart contract and used them.

We developed FMN token and now this token is used in the site what we have done.

This is one part of betting and game site and client is satisfying this result.

## **Education**

### 2009-04 - 2013-02 Associate of Science: Computer Science

University of Virginia – United States
Bachelor of Applied Science of Computer engineering- 2012